[{"question":"What is the formula for lithium oxide","correctAnswer":"Li<sub>2</sub>O","wrongAnswers":["LiO","LiO<sub>2</sub>"]},{"question":"What is the formula for lithium sulfide","correctAnswer":"Li<sub>2</sub>S","wrongAnswers":["LiS","LiS<sub>2</sub>"]},{"question":"What is the formula for lithium fluoride","correctAnswer":"LiF","wrongAnswers":["Li<sub>2</sub>F","LiF<sub>2</sub>"]},{"question":"What is the formula for lithium chloride","correctAnswer":"LiCl","wrongAnswers":["Li<sub>2</sub>Cl","LiCl<sub>2</sub>"]},{"question":"What is the formula for lithium bromide","correctAnswer":"LiBr","wrongAnswers":["Li<sub>2</sub>Br","LiBr<sub>2</sub>"]},{"question":"What is the formula for lithium iodide","correctAnswer":"LiI","wrongAnswers":["Li<sub>2</sub>I","LiI<sub>2</sub>"]},{"question":"What is the formula for sodium oxide","correctAnswer":"Na<sub>2</sub>O","wrongAnswers":["NaO","NaO<sub>2</sub>"]},{"question":"What is the formula for sodium sulfide","correctAnswer":"Na<sub>2</sub>S","wrongAnswers":["NaS","NaS<sub>2</sub>"]},{"question":"What is the formula for sodium fluoride","correctAnswer":"NaF","wrongAnswers":["Na<sub>2</sub>F","NaF<sub>2</sub>"]},{"question":"What is the formula for sodium chloride","correctAnswer":"NaCl","wrongAnswers":["Na<sub>2</sub>Cl","NaCl<sub>2</sub>"]},{"question":"What is the formula for sodium bromide","correctAnswer":"NaBr","wrongAnswers":["Na<sub>2</sub>Br","NaBr<sub>2</sub>"]},{"question":"What is the formula for sodium iodide","correctAnswer":"NaI","wrongAnswers":["Na<sub>2</sub>I","NaI<sub>2</sub>"]},{"question":"What is the formula for potassium oxide","correctAnswer":"K<sub>2</sub>O","wrongAnswers":["KO","KO<sub>2</sub>"]},{"question":"What is the formula for potassium sulfide","correctAnswer":"K<sub>2</sub>S","wrongAnswers":["KS","KS<sub>2</sub>"]},{"question":"What is the formula for potassium fluoride","correctAnswer":"KF","wrongAnswers":["K<sub>2</sub>F","KF<sub>2</sub>"]},{"question":"What is the formula for potassium chloride","correctAnswer":"KCl","wrongAnswers":["K<sub>2</sub>Cl","KCl<sub>2</sub>"]},{"question":"What is the formula for potassium bromide","correctAnswer":"KBr","wrongAnswers":["K<sub>2</sub>Br","KBr<sub>2</sub>"]},{"question":"What is the formula for potassium iodide","correctAnswer":"KI","wrongAnswers":["K<sub>2</sub>I","KI<sub>2</sub>"]},{"question":"What is the formula for rubidium oxide","correctAnswer":"Rb<sub>2</sub>O","wrongAnswers":["RbO","RbO<sub>2</sub>"]},{"question":"What is the formula for rubidium sulfide","correctAnswer":"Rb<sub>2</sub>S","wrongAnswers":["RbS","RbS<sub>2</sub>"]},{"question":"What is the formula for rubidium fluoride","correctAnswer":"RbF","wrongAnswers":["Rb<sub>2</sub>F","RbF<sub>2</sub>"]},{"question":"What is the formula for rubidium chloride","correctAnswer":"RbCl","wrongAnswers":["Rb<sub>2</sub>Cl","RbCl<sub>2</sub>"]},{"question":"What is the formula for rubidium bromide","correctAnswer":"RbBr","wrongAnswers":["Rb<sub>2</sub>Br","RbBr<sub>2</sub>"]},{"question":"What is the formula for rubidium iodide","correctAnswer":"RbI","wrongAnswers":["Rb<sub>2</sub>I","RbI<sub>2</sub>"]},{"question":"What is the formula for caesium oxide","correctAnswer":"Cs<sub>2</sub>O","wrongAnswers":["CsO","CsO<sub>2</sub>"]},{"question":"What is the formula for caesium sulfide","correctAnswer":"Cs<sub>2</sub>S","wrongAnswers":["CsS","CsS<sub>2</sub>"]},{"question":"What is the formula for caesium fluoride","correctAnswer":"CsF","wrongAnswers":["Cs<sub>2</sub>F","CsF<sub>2</sub>"]},{"question":"What is the formula for caesium chloride","correctAnswer":"CsCl","wrongAnswers":["Cs<sub>2</sub>Cl","CsCl<sub>2</sub>"]},{"question":"What is the formula for caesium bromide","correctAnswer":"CsBr","wrongAnswers":["Cs<sub>2</sub>Br","CsBr<sub>2</sub>"]},{"question":"What is the formula for caesium iodide","correctAnswer":"CsI","wrongAnswers":["Cs<sub>2</sub>I","CsI<sub>2</sub>"]},{"question":"What is the formula for magnesium oxide","correctAnswer":"MgO","wrongAnswers":["Mg<sub>2</sub>O","MgO<sub>2</sub>"]},{"question":"What is the formula for magnesium sulfide","correctAnswer":"MgS","wrongAnswers":["Mg<sub>2</sub>S","MgS<sub>2</sub>"]},{"question":"What is the formula for magnesium fluoride","correctAnswer":"MgF<sub>2</sub>","wrongAnswers":["Mg<sub>2</sub>F","MgF"]},{"question":"What is the formula for magnesium chloride","correctAnswer":"MgCl<sub>2</sub>","wrongAnswers":["Mg<sub>2</sub>Cl","MgCl"]},{"question":"What is the formula for magnesium bromide","correctAnswer":"MgBr<sub>2</sub>","wrongAnswers":["Mg<sub>2</sub>Br","MgBr"]},{"question":"What is the formula for magnesium iodide","correctAnswer":"MgI<sub>2</sub>","wrongAnswers":["Mg<sub>2</sub>I","MgI"]},{"question":"What is the formula for calcium oxide","correctAnswer":"CaO","wrongAnswers":["Ca<sub>2</sub>O","CaO<sub>2</sub>"]},{"question":"What is the formula for calcium sulfide","correctAnswer":"CaS","wrongAnswers":["Ca<sub>2</sub>S","CaS<sub>2</sub>"]},{"question":"What is the formula for calcium fluoride","correctAnswer":"CaF<sub>2</sub>","wrongAnswers":["Ca<sub>2</sub>F","CaF"]},{"question":"What is the formula for calcium chloride","correctAnswer":"CaCl<sub>2</sub>","wrongAnswers":["Ca<sub>2</sub>Cl","CaCl"]},{"question":"What is the formula for calcium bromide","correctAnswer":"CaBr<sub>2</sub>","wrongAnswers":["Ca<sub>2</sub>Br","CaBr"]},{"question":"What is the formula for calcium iodide","correctAnswer":"CaI<sub>2</sub>","wrongAnswers":["Ca<sub>2</sub>I","CaI"]},{"question":"What is the formula for strontium oxide","correctAnswer":"SrO","wrongAnswers":["Sr<sub>2</sub>O","SrO<sub>2</sub>"]},{"question":"What is the formula for strontium sulfide","correctAnswer":"SrS","wrongAnswers":["Sr<sub>2</sub>S","SrS<sub>2</sub>"]},{"question":"What is the formula for strontium fluoride","correctAnswer":"SrF<sub>2</sub>","wrongAnswers":["Sr<sub>2</sub>F","SrF"]},{"question":"What is the formula for strontium chloride","correctAnswer":"SrCl<sub>2</sub>","wrongAnswers":["Sr<sub>2</sub>Cl","SrCl"]},{"question":"What is the formula for strontium bromide","correctAnswer":"SrBr<sub>2</sub>","wrongAnswers":["Sr<sub>2</sub>Br","SrBr"]},{"question":"What is the formula for strontium iodide","correctAnswer":"SrI<sub>2</sub>","wrongAnswers":["Sr<sub>2</sub>I","SrI"]},{"question":"What is the formula for barium oxide","correctAnswer":"BaO","wrongAnswers":["Ba<sub>2</sub>O","BaO<sub>2</sub>"]},{"question":"What is the formula for barium sulfide","correctAnswer":"BaS","wrongAnswers":["Ba<sub>2</sub>S","BaS<sub>2</sub>"]},{"question":"What is the formula for barium fluoride","correctAnswer":"BaF<sub>2</sub>","wrongAnswers":["Ba<sub>2</sub>F","BaF"]},{"question":"What is the formula for barium chloride","correctAnswer":"BaCl<sub>2</sub>","wrongAnswers":["Ba<sub>2</sub>Cl","BaCl"]},{"question":"What is the formula for barium bromide","correctAnswer":"BaBr<sub>2</sub>","wrongAnswers":["Ba<sub>2</sub>Br","BaBr"]},{"question":"What is the formula for barium iodide","correctAnswer":"BaI<sub>2</sub>","wrongAnswers":["Ba<sub>2</sub>I","BaI"]}]